<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://rlaplaza.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://rlaplaza.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-07-29T11:54:39+00:00</updated><id>https://rlaplaza.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">rlaplaza and crew</title><subtitle>A lab working on machine learning and computational tools to unveil the secrets of matter</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello!</title><link href="https://rlaplaza.github.io/2025/07/26/Hello-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello!" /><published>2025-07-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2025-07-29T11:53:24+00:00</updated><id>https://rlaplaza.github.io/2025/07/26/Hello-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://rlaplaza.github.io/2025/07/26/Hello-world.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hey! I recently moved to Seville to start my group at the IIQ. Understandably, this is a fairly new experience for me. That said, this is a wonderful place to take this important step.</p>

<p>Seville feels like the kind of city that gets under your skin and refuses to let go. You’ve got one of Europe’s most stunning historic centers right at your doorstep - the cathedral, the Alcázar, those winding medieval streets that seem to lead somewhere magical every time. The food scene is incredible, not just tourist-trap restaurants but real neighborhood bars where locals gather for tapas and conversation that stretches late into the night. The weather means you can actually enjoy outdoor life most of the year, and there’s this infectious energy going on. I guess if you know you know.</p>

<p>Yes, it can get crowded, and the summers are intense, but they say once you experience that perfect Seville evening you understand why people fall completely in love with this place.</p>

<p>Well, simply put, I hope to revisit this short memo in a few years and contrast my impressions then. I also hope to have some science to discuss by then. Exciting things are coming!</p>]]></content><author><name>rlaplaza</name></author><category term="random," /><category term="chemistry," /><category term="computational" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey! I recently moved to Seville to start my group at the IIQ. Understandably, this is a fairly new experience for me. That said, this is a wonderful place to take this important step.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://rlaplaza.github.io/images/post.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://rlaplaza.github.io/images/post.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>